http://www.hartgem.com/privacy-policy

WOOCS v.2.3.0
NavigationAccount0NavigationEngagement RingsBridal SetsSolitaire DiamondSide Stone DiamondsTrinity DiamondsIndividual RingsSolitaire DiamondSide Stone DiamondsTrinity DiamondsWedding RingsDiamond BandsBy Stone MountBead SetBezel SetChannel SetProng SetLadies BandsMens BandsHis and Hers SetPrincess CutRound CutAll Wedding SetsWedding BandsWhite GoldTwo-toneTri-colourPlain BandRingsSignet RingsLadies Signet RingsMen’s Signet RingsUnisex Signet RingsInitial RingsLadies Initial RingsMen’s Initial RingsShop All Initial RingsPromise RingsSolitaireTrinityAll Promise RingsStone RingsBy Stone TypeAmethystBlack OnyxBlood StoneBlue MasonicCitrinEmeraldFalcon EyeJadeGarnetRubySapphireYellow TopazAll Stone RingsJewelleryBraceletsBy Stone CutPrincess CutRound CutBy Stone TypeDiamond BraceletsEmerald BraceletsRuby BraceletsSapphire BraceletsEarringsPrincess CutRound CutShop All EarringsNecklacesPrincess Cut StoneRound Cut StoneAll NecklacesGift IdeasBy OccasionMother’s DayBirthdayGraduationAnniversaryBy Jewellery TypeType of GiftBraceletsEarringsGemstone RingsInitial RingsNecklaces & PendantsPromise RingsSignet RingsAll Gift IdeasHeart GiftsNecklacesRingsEarringsAll Heart Jewellery
Privacy Policy
Hartgem Privacy Policy
Hartgem Privacy Policy
Your privacy is critically important to us.
Hartgem Jewellery is located at:
Hartgem Jewellery
3635 Loyalist Dr Mississauga
Ontario, Canada
+1 877-513-7655
It is Hartgem Jewellery’s policy to respect your privacy regarding any information we may collect while operating our website. This Privacy Policy applies to https://hartgem.com/ (hereinafter, “us”, “we”, or “https://hartgem.com/”). We respect your privacy and are committed to protecting personally identifiable information you may provide us through the Website. We have adopted this privacy policy (“Privacy Policy”) to explain what information may be collected on our Website, how we use this information, and under what circumstances we may disclose the information to third parties. This Privacy Policy applies only to information we collect through the Website and does not apply to our collection of information from other sources.
This Privacy Policy, together with the Terms and conditions posted on our Website, set forth the general rules and policies governing your use of our Website. Depending on your activities when visiting our Website, you may be required to agree to additional terms and conditions.
Website Visitors
Like most website operators, Hartgem Jewellery collects non-personally-identifying information of the sort that web browsers and servers typically make available, such as the browser type, language preference, referring site, and the date and time of each visitor request. Hartgem Jewellery’s purpose in collecting non-personally identifying information is to better understand how Hartgem Jewellery’s visitors use its website. From time to time, Hartgem Jewellery may release non-personally-identifying information in the aggregate, e.g., by publishing a report on trends in the usage of its website.
Hartgem Jewellery also collects potentially personally-identifying information like Internet Protocol (IP) addresses for logged in users and for users leaving comments on https://hartgem.com/ blog posts. Hartgem Jewellery only discloses logged in user and commenter IP addresses under the same circumstances that it uses and discloses personally-identifying information as described below.
Gathering of Personally-Identifying Information
Certain visitors to Hartgem Jewellery’s websites choose to interact with Hartgem Jewellery in ways that require Hartgem Jewellery to gather personally-identifying information. The amount and type of information that Hartgem Jewellery gathers depends on the nature of the interaction. For example, we ask visitors who sign up for a newsletter at https://hartgem.com/ to provide a name and email address.
Security
The security of your Personal Information is important to us, but remember that no method of transmission over the Internet, or method of electronic storage is 100% secure. While we strive to use commercially acceptable means to protect your Personal Information, we cannot guarantee its absolute security.
Protection of Certain Personally-Identifying Information
Hartgem Jewellery discloses potentially personally-identifying and personally-identifying information only to those of its employees, contractors and affiliated organizations that (i) need to know that information in order to process it on Hartgem Jewellery’s behalf or to provide services available at Hartgem Jewellery’s website, and (ii) that have agreed not to disclose it to others. Some of those employees, contractors and affiliated organizations may be located outside of your home country; by using Hartgem Jewellery’s website, you consent to the transfer of such information to them. Hartgem Jewellery will not rent or sell potentially personally-identifying and personally-identifying information to anyone. Other than to its employees, contractors and affiliated organizations, as described above, Hartgem Jewellery discloses potentially personally-identifying and personally-identifying information only in response to a subpoena, court order or other governmental request, or when Hartgem Jewellery believes in good faith that disclosure is reasonably necessary to protect the property or rights of Hartgem Jewellery, third parties or the public at large.
If you are a registered user of https://hartgem.com/ and have supplied your email address, Hartgem Jewellery may occasionally send you an email to tell you about new features, solicit your feedback, or just keep you up to date with what’s going on with Hartgem Jewellery and our products. We primarily use our blog to communicate this type of information, so we expect to keep this type of email to a minimum. If you send us a request (for example via a support email or via one of our feedback mechanisms), we reserve the right to publish it in order to help us clarify or respond to your request or to help us support other users. Hartgem Jewellery takes all measures reasonably necessary to protect against the unauthorized access, use, alteration or destruction of potentially personally-identifying and personally-identifying information.
Aggregated Statistic
Hartgem Jewellery may collect statistics about the behavior of visitors to its website. Hartgem Jewellery may display this information publicly or provide it to others. However, Hartgem Jewellery does not disclose your personally-identifying information.
Cookies
To enrich and perfect your online experience, Hartgem Jewellery uses “Cookies”, similar technologies and services provided by others to display personalized content, appropriate advertising and store your preferences on your computer.
A cookie is a string of information that a website stores on a visitor’s computer, and that the visitor’s browser provides to the website each time the visitor returns. Hartgem Jewellery uses cookies to help Hartgem Jewellery identify and track visitors, their usage of https://hartgem.com/, and their website access preferences. Hartgem Jewellery visitors who do not wish to have cookies placed on their computers should set their browsers to refuse cookies before using Hartgem Jewellery’s websites, with the drawback that certain features of Hartgem Jewellery’s websites may not function properly without the aid of cookies.
By continuing to navigate our website without changing your cookie settings, you hereby acknowledge and agree to Hartgem Jewellery’s use of cookies.
E-commerce
Those who engage in transactions with Hartgem Jewellery – by purchasing Hartgem Jewellery’s services or products, are asked to provide additional information, including as necessary the personal and financial information required to process those transactions. In each case, Hartgem Jewellery collects such information only insofar as is necessary or appropriate to fulfill the purpose of the visitor’s interaction with Hartgem Jewellery. Hartgem Jewellery does not disclose personally-identifying information other than as described below. And visitors can always refuse to supply personally-identifying information, with the caveat that it may prevent them from engaging in certain website-related activities.
Business Transfers
If Hartgem Jewellery, or substantially all of its assets, were acquired, or in the unlikely event that Hartgem Jewellery goes out of business or enters bankruptcy, user information would be one of the assets that is transferred or acquired by a third party. You acknowledge that such transfers may occur, and that any acquirer of Hartgem Jewellery may continue to use your personal information as set forth in this policy.
Privacy Policy Changes
Although most changes are likely to be minor, Hartgem Jewellery may change its Privacy Policy from time to time, and in Hartgem Jewellery’s sole discretion. Hartgem Jewellery encourages visitors to frequently check this page for any changes to its Privacy Policy. Your continued use of this site after any change in this Privacy Policy will constitute your acceptance of such change.
OUR STORY About Hartgem
CONNECT
Instagram
Facebook
LEGAL Return Policy
Terms and Conditions
Privacy Policy
GET IN TOUCH
Signet Rings
Ladies Signet RingsMen’s Signet RingsUnisex Signet Rings Back
Initial Rings
Ladies Initial RingsMen’s Initial RingsShop All Initial Rings Back
Promise Rings
SolitaireTrinityAll Promise Rings Back
Stone Rings
By Stone Type
AmethystBlack OnyxBlood StoneBlue MasonicCitrinEmeraldFalcon EyeJadeGarnetRubySapphireYellow Topaz Back
All Stone Rings Back
Back
Jewellery
Bracelets
By Stone Cut
Princess CutRound Cut Back
By Stone Type
Diamond BraceletsEmerald BraceletsRuby BraceletsSapphire Bracelets Back
Shop All Bracelets Back
Earrings
Princess CutRound CutShop All Earrings Back
Necklaces
Princess Cut StoneRound Cut StoneAll Necklaces Back
Back
Gift Ideas
By Occasion
Mother’s DayBirthdayGraduationAnniversary Back
By Jewellery Type
Type of Gift
BraceletsEarringsGemstone RingsInitial RingsNecklaces & PendantsPromise RingsSignet Rings Back
All Gift Ideas Back
Heart Gifts
NecklacesRingsEarringsAll Heart Jewellery Back
Back
× Close Panel
Enjoy FREE SHIPPING on all orders over $750! Enjoy FREE SHIPPING on all orders over $750!
GET MY DISCOUNTGet 10% off your purchase & exclusive access to a weekly 20% off product pick!By clicking "Get My Coupon", you agree to receive our newsletter with promos & sales. You can opt out at any time.
Privacy PolicyNo thanks, I don't want awesome deals and promotions. Let me shop!10% OFF & EXCLUSIVE DEALSGET MY DISCOUNTGet 10% off your purchase & exclusive access to a weekly 20% off product pick!By clicking "Get My Coupon", you agree to receive our newsletter. You can opt out at any time.
Privacy Policy.No thanks, I don't want awesome deals and promotions.10% OFF PROMO
